[opening theme song playing]
♪ Hey ♪
♪ Yo ♪
♪ Mmm-hmm, come on ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Left the school behind
Into the world, a sign ♪
♪ Put the weights on a thrilling ride ♪
♪ Uh ♪
♪ Ow! ♪
♪ Oh-ooh, yeah ♪
♪ Yo ♪
- ♪ Come on ♪
- ♪ Move the world, move, move ♪
♪ Now, look, if I step into the world
We can have some fun ♪
♪ Yo ♪
♪ Uh, move the world, move, move ♪
♪ Now, look, if I step into the world
Let you have some fun ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Mmm-hmm, right ♪
BAMBI IS ALIVE AND WELL
KINES INGREDIENT ANALYSIS
[Louis] Myosin, actin, myogen,
then tongkat, and phosphate of maca?
Is that it?
It is. At least for the meat
and bone part.
This stuff is
in a commercially available drink?
No wonder it causes meat intoxication.
But that's the thing.
There's not enough in it
to set its drinkers off like that.
Seriously?
Then, could it be something else?
[Chloe] I think so.
My theory is that it's somehow
reacting with another substance
to light up the central nervous system.
So it needs some kind of catalyst.
[Chloe] Hmm.
Considering that herbivores don't seem
to show any symptoms when they drink it,
it must be something unique to carnivores.
Then what is it?
That's outside my area of expertise.
Still, I know a researcher
who could probably help you out.
Do they work at your lab too?
Mmm-mmm. He, uh, works somewhere else.
And he's sort of...
Uh, what is it?
He's very talented, but he is a bit shady.
Would you mind introducing me--
- [crackles]
- [yelps, groans]
Hey. What happened?
Are you okay? Answer me, please.
Do you hear me?
Louis!
[strains] I'm all right.
Could you send me his contact details?
[ends call]
[groaning]
What's going on?
I know I fed everything
from the knee down to Legoshi.
Could something have happened
to him? Legoshi?
CALL ENDED
KOPI LUWAK RESEARCH CENTER
DESHICO
HAPPY & HEAVEN
JUNGLE THEATER
[Luna] We said we don't know.
You really have no idea
who that big bad wolf was?
How many times do I have to tell you?
The owner set us up and we did our thing.
[Miguel] Come on.
Do you think we're the type of idiots
who'd nod their heads and walk away
after a half-assed story like that?
You're the type of idiots to keep us here
after we told the truth.
Screw this.
Given your line of work,
we'd hate to do anything
that might leave a mark
on those spectacular bodies of yours.
So just tell us. It'll make this easier.
We don't know shit!
[Free clicks tongue] That's a damn shame.
Have it your way, then.
[Cosmo gasps]
Sorry about this,
but we can't go home empty-handed.
By the time we all got here,
you two had already
made yourselves scarce.
- [Luna] Huh?
- Got that?
I made a promise to a former boss of ours.
I told him that I'd keep you both safe.
[Cosmo] Was your former boss
that little fawn boy?
The Shishi-Gumi always keeps its promises.
[both exhale]
[Free] We'll find our souvenirs
somewhere else.
Hey, we had orders to kill those two.
- You sure about this?
- [Free grunts]
Yep, it's all good.
[Free] Hmm?
- [Free grunts]
- [Agata] Huh?
[Free panting]
[panting]
[Louis] Damn it, Zoozle.
At least factor in places
like the Black Market
when you calculate your routes. [groans]
If they catch me here, I'm done for.
[pants]
[Free] Hmm. [gasps softly]
- [crackles]
- [grunts, sighs]
[beeps]
[Louis] This needs some maintenance.
[gasps]
[Free growls softly]
Boss?
[huffs]
[Free] Hmm.
I can't imagine you've forgotten
our very last agreement.
Promised you that if I ever saw you
in the Black Market again,
I'd kill you on the spot.
Yeah. I guess I failed to hold up
my end of the bargain.
Do it.
[Free] Damn it. Why does it have to be me?
[Louis] Don't hesitate.
[Free] First Ibuki, now him.
Why am I always the one
who has to pull the trigger?
[Louis] What's with that look?
[scoffs] Aren't you the king of beasts?
[Free] Not even a hint of fear
on your face.
I knew all along
you really were the best boss we ever had.
[gunshot]
[Free exhales shakily]
[antler clatters]
[Louis] I shed my antlers.
Is it that time already?
Sorry to throw off your aim there.
Go ahead.
[Free chuckles]
I said I'd kill you
if I saw you again, correct?
That was the promise, wasn't it?
But from where I'm standing, you don't
look like anybody I've ever seen before.
[laughing]
- I've missed you so much!
- Hey!
- Free really might kill him.
- [Louis] Enough!
- Stop it already!
- [all laughing]
- [Jimma] Oh. Those are sick!
- Hey! [exclaims playfully]
[Agata] Look at you without your antlers.
You're like a fawn.
Can it.
Man, what a waste.
They grew so beautifully.
So, what will you do with these?
If you want to keep them,
they're all yours.
- Whoo! [laughs, exclaims]
- Yes! Ex-boss is the best!
By the way,
as long as we're patching you up,
how's your leg?
Noticed you were walking funny.
Oh, yeah. I lost my right leg.
- [all] What?
- Huh?
- It's so shiny!
- [all exclaiming]
[Louis sighs] I'm used to losing
body parts,
what with shedding antlers and all.
It's not a big deal.
More importantly,
I want to know
why you guys look so emaciated.
[sighs]
Thing is, we're explicitly limited
to eating meat two times a month.
Just another exciting
new Shishi-Gumi rule.
And if you sneak some
behind that asshole's back, he'll know,
and then... [clicks tongue]
"That asshole"?
Anyway, what brought you
to the Black Market?
Oh...
Uh, the Kopi... Hang on.
[all] "Kopi Luwak"?
[all exhale]
Do you know the place?
[Jimma] Uh, yeah.
[whistling in distance]
- It's the boss!
- [Victor] He's here early.
Huh?
It stinks, but it should cover your scent
while we hide you.
[whistling grows louder]
[whistling stops]
Guess what! I brought you kittens
a little souvenir today.
[lions gasp]
[Melon] Yeah, he may have been
an absolute failure as a guard, but...
[inhales sharply] I think he should
make for a decent decoration.
- [all gasp]
- [Melon] All right, then.
Let's have ourselves
a round of stripper steaks.
[Louis] A gazelle?
No, those fangs...
A mix?
[Melon] Huh? What the hell is this?
We arrived too late.
The strippers got away.
So, in turn, we took what was owed
from the club's owner instead.
Huh.
And you actually thought this would make
for an acceptable replacement
for the dinner I asked for?
[Agata] We're getting paid
pretty well there.
[Melon] Hmm?
But even if we weren't,
we're not so desperate for food
that we'd eat someone on our turf.
Well, well.
I must admit I'm impressed.
[inhales sharply]
You really put a lot of thought
into how your actions
might play out here, didn't you?
- [splutters nervously] Uh, yeah.
- [chuckles]
- [Melon grunts]
- [Agata screaming]
Agata, the Congo lion, 26 years old.
You truly are the baby of the Shishi-Gumi.
[screaming]
Ah, a dull little boy
who clings to his imagined
sense of lionly pride
because it allows him to pose
as being an adult.
Anyway. Free.
Uh-- Yes?
There's an outsider
in this room, isn't there?
Hmm?
Tell me, how stupid
do you idiots think I am?
I could smell them as soon
as I walked in, you lying little shits.
- Come on. What are you sitting around for?
- [groaning]
Bring out our little visitor
so I can get a good look at him.
Our guest or Agata.
Time for you to choose
who I'll be serving for dinner.
I can't hear you!
- [Louis] I have to show myself.
- [Miguel] I'm sorry, boss.
Huh?
Ah. Ha!
I thought that I smelled deer.
What do you know?
Those antlers are so fresh
that the blood on them is still wet.
Care to explain?
I disobeyed your orders, boss.
Couldn't keep my cravings in check.
I found a deer on the Black Market,
and I ate it.
I won't make excuses.
Because there is no excuse.
Carnivores like us,
we're foolish creatures
led only by instinct.
That's all we are.
As a singular mix
of carnivore and herbivore,
you could be called a perfect creature,
and I am but a mere lion.
I couldn't even follow a simple rule
like only eating meat twice a month.
[Louis sighs]
But I promise,
if you give me another chance,
- I swear...
- [gasps]
[Miguel] I swear that
I'll never eat meat again
so that I can work on becoming
even slightly as perfect as you.
[groans]
For a foolish creature,
you're using your head rather well.
[breath trembles]
I was hoping to enjoy
a nice, relaxing dinner, but...
[inhales sharply] now that Yahya's aware
of my connection with you kittens,
I probably shouldn't hang around
this place for too long.
Huh?
KOPI LUWAK RESEARCH CENTER
[chuckles nervously] I've got holes
in my pockets lately, I guess.
Is that so?
Anyone ever tell you that your handwriting
is weak and skinny like an herbivore's?
[Melon whistling]
[Agata grunts, yells]
Who'd have thought
you were such a performer?
Never knew you had that groveling in you.
[Miguel chuckles] It was nothing.
- [rattling]
- [all] Huh?
I don't know what to say.
Anything but freaking thanks.
We wouldn't be lions
if we didn't look out for our pride.
So, your next stop is Kopi Luwak?
Yeah.
I've been looking into Kines.
[all sighing]
CENTRAL HOSPITAL
LARGE ANIMAL WARD
- [machine beeping]
- [groans]
Huh?
Huh.
Mmm.
[gasps] That's right! Melon shot me.
And I guess someone brought me here.
[gasps]
Tha-- That's me!
Huh?
[shudders]
[exhales]
So, does this mean
I'm stuck between life and death?
Am I... Am I going to die?
[sighs frustratingly] If I knew this was
going to happen, I would've...
I would've given Haru that kiss
when I still had the chance.
Ah, sorry, Haru.
I wonder if she'll cry
when she hears that I died.
Nah, she'll probably just be mad.
[sighs heavily]
[female] Isn't it a little soon
to be giving up like that?
Well, I don't know. Just look at me.
Huh?
Mom?
I can't believe it.
My mom died six years ago,
but she's standing right in front of me.
Look at how big you've gotten, Legoshi.
[Legoshi] Wait, is this...
You silly boy.
You know,
you always used to be so reserved.
Now you leap into danger whenever you can.
Well, I...
You really do know
how to make a mother worry.
I'm sorry.
But I just couldn't stand there
and let Melon keep calling himself
a freak, a thing, an abomination
because I know that you're mixed too,
and, you know, if Haru and I decide
to have a kid someday,
obviously, they'd be mixed.
It kind of made me wonder
if our kid would see themself
as some kind of abomination.
Well, that is what they'd be.
What?
[footsteps approaching]
[Yahya sighs]
[Yahya] It's been five days.
You need something in your stomach.
[sighs]
[Leanno] Your grandfather
was a Komodo dragon,
and your grandmother was a gray wolf.
And together, they gave birth to me.
Given their rather unique pairing,
people were naturally curious.
They wanted to see what sort
of ugly creature the two created.
[Legoshi] Hmm.
Of course, much to their chagrin,
I grew up to be a beautiful wolf,
and a fine model at that.
[Legoshi] Oh, hey, I remember these.
Grandpa must've put them in the scrapbook.
[Leanno] I'll have you know
that back in my day,
"Leanno the Gray Wolf" was quite
the sensation in the modeling world.
[Legoshi] Hmm. Yeah, I can see it.
You wouldn't believe
how in I was. [chuckles]
- That's why...
- Huh?
[melancholy music playing]
I don't want anyone to know
my dad's a Komodo dragon.
We're going to have to keep you
a secret. I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it, sweetheart.
At least you and I can share a nice meal
without my venom causing any problems.
And us eating together,
well, that alone makes me happy.
Just live your life.
[Leanno] I was truly loved.
Even then, I was afraid.
No matter what I did or said,
Komodo dragon blood
still flowed through my veins.
[humming]
[chuckling]
Looking good. [gasps]
[screams]
The doctor told me it was
some rare genetic something or other
that manifested with age
and that there was nothing
that could be done.
- [female 1] Ew, do you see that?
- [female 2] Disgusting.
- [gasps]
- [female 3] Don't come near me.
- [whimpering]
- [female 3] How filthy.
- She's venomous. Don't touch her.
- [whimpering]
[male 1] Put her down
if she's that dangerous.
- [male 2] Stay back.
- [male 3] Just die already.
[Leanno whimpering]
[Leanno] I was neither wolf nor lizard.
No. I had no place in this world.
Just a strange creature without a name.
An abomination.
And so...
[melancholy music continues playing]
[females whispering indistinctly]
[Leanno] The night before I killed myself,
I came to snuggle with you
for a little while.
I'm so sorry that I didn't say anything.
I suppose I was a selfish mother,
right up until the very end.
[Legoshi] I should have said something.
- I'm sorry.
- [Leanno] What?
[Legoshi] I was...
I was awake that night.
I thought your scales and your fur,
both looked so beautiful.
[Leanno gasps] You did?
[Legoshi] I wanted to press my cheek
to yours, to turn around and hug you.
For you to hug me.
Because in all the world,
you're the only mom I've got.
[Leanno cries] That makes me so happy.
[sniffles] Thank you.
That night, I thought
if I didn't say anything,
if I didn't look at you,
it would make things
easier on you somehow.
I had no idea
that's what you were thinking about.
[Legoshi] Mmm.
[sighs deeply] Why didn't I just
turn around that night?
Oh, Mom, I wish I could have told you
what I thought.
Thank you for that.
And you're right.
There's a chance that
if I'd heard those words,
things could've gone differently.
But I'm afraid I can't undo what I did.
And that's why it's so important
that you reach out to all the mixed beasts
who are suffering in the world.
And do it in your own words.
In my own words?
Yes, in your unique way.
Think of all of the different scars
on your body.
Each and every one of them
is just like another one of your words.
Oh.
I know what I want to do. It's clear now.
Then you better not forget it.
You've inherited blood
from both me and your grandpa.
You're kinder and stronger
than anybody else.
You think so?
Legoshi, I'll always love you.
Hmm?
[music ends]
[both gasp]
[Gosha] Legoshi?
[Gosha] Hmm.
[howling]
[closing theme song playing]
♪ Just like a new melody ♪
♪ Keep it beating on and on ♪
♪ I don't want to live without it ♪
♪ You give me the strength inside ♪
♪ Some things aren't meant to be ♪
♪ You say it like you know ♪
♪ But I really want you ♪
♪ I want you to see it the way I do ♪
♪ 'Cause every time I think about you ♪
♪ My heartbeat goes a-risin' ♪
- ♪ And I just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till I... ♪
♪ Till I die ♪
♪ There's nothing
That can beat like this ♪
♪ Faster as I close my eyes ♪
- ♪ Just want to feel like this ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ Till the... ♪
♪ Till the night ♪
♪ Now as long as you are here by my side ♪
♪ Run, run, run ♪
♪ I keep walking on ♪
♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
- ♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh ♪
- ♪ Walking on, on, walking on, on ♪
- ♪ Run, run, run ♪
- ♪ I keep walking on ♪